So hey guys good morning welcome back you
explore d on kar today as I
told you that through ICC Home Guard policy
I had booked my health checkup
which is included in my policy itself and
means it is complimentary color cup its
appointment booked at 9:00 so right now it
is time for 9 o'clock how many minutes I billed for
two minutes
and
2 minutes time will get an appointment at 9:00
well
what is happening
[sangeet] I am
late
[sangeet]
[sangeet] so
I had informed
these people earlier in this matter friends so let's see
okay so anyway let's see now it remains to be seen at
what time these people will be able to reach it
remains to be seen whether they are fine and how much
[sangeet]
after this
breakfast preparations are going on so today's
breakfast is paneer paratha so
we will
go okay
[sangeet]
so gas we have help checkup test is
complete and
I will already give him out of iPhone that it
should be deducted because he  They
came after 15 minutes at 9:15 exactly at 9:15 they had
come here,
we have got the ECGC left sarees done, in this process the
total time taken by three of us is
fine
[Music] [Music
]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music] in that just actually he is still
a little fresh, he is still
small, so we don't have to buy a new cycle
for that so at this date we will have to do this cycle a
little
and he will grow a little
[Music] [Music
]
software today
[Music] so
gas this think this is it this means
hanging off today there is
bill meet tomorrow and late block
look he is shouting from behind
so today was a good day we should go to
Agarwal Sweets, we have finished
all the food, it is good food, roti
etc. roti gram sabji, it is available there, he will
make it, I was in the mood, I will not come, actually almost
our channel also had an
office, so he went to the office  I had completed it, hadn't I?
Tomorrow's agenda is that
I have to take Suresh along, his skating
classes are about to start and there is a lot more to
sign off on today.